zinghr.com 2016-08-05

# Privacy Policy

ZingHR ("We") are committed to protecting the privacy of the personally-identifiable information that we collect from you as you use this ZingHR Website. The scope of our commitment is detailed in this Privacy Policy. By submitting information, you agree to allow ZingHR use of such information as described herein. Please also see our Disclaimer.

## Use of Personally-identifiable Information

ZingHR uses your personally-identifiable information to fulfill your requests for information, to evaluate any job applications or other employment-related inquiries that you may submit, or for such other business purposes as you may initiate or request. We may keep any of your personally-identifiable information on file and use it to contact you for recruiting or business purposes. ZingHR also uses personally identifiable information to perform statistical analyses of user behavior in order to measure interest in specific areas and information posted on our Site. ZingHR uses personally-identifiable information collected from cookies and IP addresses as described below. ZingHR may provide your personally-identifiable information to any of its affiliates worldwide for such purposes.

## Third Party Disclosure

ZingHR shall not intentionally disclose or transfer (and shall take reasonable steps to protect the confidentiality and security, and to prevent the unauthorized or accidental disclosure of) your personally-identifiable information to third parties (i.e., persons or entities that are not affiliates of ZingHR), whether for such third parties' marketing purposes or otherwise, subject only to the following four exceptions: ZingHR may disclose your personally-identifiable information to third parties in the event that such disclosure is required by the laws, rules, or regulations of any nation, state, or other applicable jurisdiction; ZingHR may disclose your contact information to third parties as appropriate for ZingHR to make transmissions or deliveries to you; ZingHR may disclose your personally-identifiable information if, in connection with submitting the information, you consent to such disclosure; and ZingHR may disclose contact information for you in response to inquiries by bona-fide rights owners in connection with allegations of infringement of copyright or other proprietary rights arising from information you have posted on the Site or otherwise provided to ZingHR.

## Surveys & Contests

Our web site may request information for contests and surveys. Submissions of these information are entirely voluntary. You have the option to deny submission of these information. The kind of information requests is to enable contact, gather relevant data and to inform winners of the contests. The surveys ask for demographic, psychographic and other relevant details for aggregate use, to enable us to monitor business trends and provide updated information to our users.

## Data Security

ZingHR uses generally accepted standards of technology and operational security in order to protect personally-identifiable information from loss, misuse, alteration, or destruction. Only authorized ZingHR personnel are provided access to personally-identifiable information, and these employees are required to treat this information as confidential. Despite these precautions, due to the open and un-secured nature of the Internet on this portal , ZingHR cannot guarantee that unauthorized persons will not/cannot obtain access to your personally-identifiable information collected through these forms on the website . ZingHR's production operations run on the Secure Encrypted Cloud for its customers , make it absolutely secure for critical customer operations.

## Changes to Privacy Policy

By using the Site, you consent to the collection, use, and storage of your information by us in the manner described in this Privacy Policy and elsewhere on the Site. We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time which will automatically reflect on the website. You may periodically visit the Privacy Policy page on the website to see the latest policies in force.

If you have any queries about our Privacy Policy or feel that this company is not abiding by its posted Privacy Policy, please contact us at [info@zinghr.com](mailto:info@zinghr.com). Your privacy is our concern.
